<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>arjun&#39;s webpage</title>
    <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on arjun&#39;s webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cipirit.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2024-01-07-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2024-01-07-city/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>चर्चा</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/charcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 10:08:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/charcha/</guid>
      <description>बात होती है तो केवल उसकी जो स्पष्ट रूप से सभी की इंद्रियों में पंजिकृत (बहतर शब्द की गैर मौजूदगी में।) हो। तापमान, वायु का रुख, कुत्तों का भौंकना, विविद्ध प्रकार की गंधें वगैरा इस वार्तालाप के लिए उत्तम विष्य हैं। अपने निजी दर्षन इस चर्चा में न ही लायें तो अच्छा है। मालूम नहीं कब कोई छोटी सी टिप्पणी या राय आऐगी और माहौल को एक तनाव से भर देगी। एसा तनाव जो स्वयं को शंका के घेरे में दाल देगा, कि कहीं आप ही तो किसी प्रकार के अधर्मी नहीं?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whimsymaxxing</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/thoughts/2024-01-01-whimsymaxxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:07:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/thoughts/2024-01-01-whimsymaxxing/</guid>
      <description>Whimsymaxxing, This new trend of people putting their childhood photos in their profile pictures is another form of whimsymaxxing. An attempt to return to their untainted child like creativity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Sisyphus</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/mr-sisyphus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:16:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/mr-sisyphus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladder</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-10-29-ladder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:39:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-10-29-ladder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The God That Failed</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-10-04-the-god-that-failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 20:59:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-10-04-the-god-that-failed/</guid>
      <description>Eucalyptus, &amp;ldquo;The God That Failed&amp;rdquo; as dubbed by the researcher N.C. Saxena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clouds</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-09-18-clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 19:43:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-09-18-clouds/</guid>
      <description>while my monsoon gently retreats </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disconnect</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/disconnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/disconnect/</guid>
      <description>Music, Mathematics and The Matrix&#xA;Earphones are like parasites. Parasites that crawl up your ear to disconnect you from the reality to hook you up to the fake world of digital entertainment stimulating your senses shielding you from the truth you are trying to run away from. Remember that old Moserbear advertisement ?&#xA;Don&#39;t like to think too much It makes me think too much It keeps my mind on my mind Don&#39;t want to see too much It makes me see too much Sometimes I&#39;d rather be blind Music itself is a very powerful thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aloo Tikki</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/aloo-tikki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:19:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/aloo-tikki/</guid>
      <description>Its the conflicting flavours, red caramelized chutney with its heavy spicy taste and the green, sour tangy refreshing coriander chutney. The hot tikki just out of the wok, straight into some chilled yoghurt. A contrast of temperature. The depth and texture of the brown deep fried tikki being contrasted by the homogenous white yoghurt. On top it may be graced by a salad dressing, of chopped onions, cabbage and pomegranate further producing opposition to the deep fried carbohydrates of the tikki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lal Kot Gaussian Edit</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/lal-kot-gaussian-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 11:06:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/lal-kot-gaussian-edit/</guid>
      <description>So, in my regular fasion I made some edits of Lal Kot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanjay Van</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-06-28-sanjay-van/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 11:00:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-06-28-sanjay-van/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dustbin</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-06-28-dustbin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 10:58:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-06-28-dustbin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lal Kot</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-06-28-lal-kot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 10:52:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-06-28-lal-kot/</guid>
      <description>Quila Lal Kot&#xA;I dont know why it is disoriented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Reaction Channels</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/music-reaction-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:33:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/music-reaction-channels/</guid>
      <description>In the recent years, music reaction channels on YouTube have become quite a thing. These channels mainly react to forms of alternative music such as rock, metal and other genres that like to go with the &amp;ldquo;its not pop music&amp;rdquo; identity.&#xA;Cultural Shock The usual consumer base of this media, largely comprises of nerdy, introverted, and in recent years (due to the desensitization of the word nerd) autistic people, which in turn largely contains Caucasian males.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Youtube Distraction Free</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/2023-06-24-make-youtube-distraction-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:05:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/2023-06-24-make-youtube-distraction-free/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, it has become increasingly hard to focus on the web. With websites and serveices now being designed to make you shuttle from one red dot to another, it has become necessary for us users to preserve our integrities as users and to not become consumers. This article will guide you to removing all sorts of distractions from YouTube, a popular video sharing website which houses a library of videos ranging from casual entertainment to perhaps the best lectures in calculus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short Video Format</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/short-video-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:47:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/short-video-format/</guid>
      <description>Against the short video format The short video format is a non consensual, habit forming, freedom infringing video format that destroys the users attention span. It takes away the users right to consent, delivers them trivial information in bite sized bits of novelty along with a hit of hormones.&#xA;The user while viewing this format loose all their freedom of choice, as videos scroll past them automatically without any decision making involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Block</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-05-26-machine-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 07:35:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/2023-05-26-machine-block/</guid>
      <description>Machine Block</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquisition of Audiophillic Equipment</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/aquisition-of-audiophillic-equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:17:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/aquisition-of-audiophillic-equipment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casio DB-36 Inverted Display Mod</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/casio-db36-inverted-display-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:21:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/casio-db36-inverted-display-mod/</guid>
      <description>I had been meaning to try an inverted display mod on one of my Casio watches, and now finally I had the time and money to get a polarizing filer and do it and see for myself&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&#xA;time&amp;hellip;.. with the reversed polarity.&#xA;In simple terms this mod i.e. modification basically takes the display, and inverts its colours. Now what does that do ? It makes me a cooler person. It is acheived by removing the old polarizing filter and putting on a new filter that blocks and allows the opposite directions of polarized light, generating this effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Site</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/2023-04-30-new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/2023-04-30-new-site/</guid>
      <description>newsite!&#xA;using hugo this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>नीम </title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/neem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/neem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:31:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/college/</guid>
      <description>A series of (incoherent) thoughts I have had since joining college. The curiculum is merely a carcass every student is assigned to drag behind them for the next four years of their life. Even the administration knows this, and they dont put too much effort into not letting the world know about it.&#xA;Exams and academics only exist to provide a goal to those who dont have a purpose to live upto (yet).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Jee Feels</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/post-jee-feels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 17:31:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/post-jee-feels/</guid>
      <description>So my first JEE attempt is complete and now I am here, writing a blog post in a (sucessfull) attempt of relaxing and chilling for one day in what seems like months since I have walked without a head full of stress. This I belive must be my reward. The only proof that I need to strengthen this belife is that today, ladies and gentlemen is the day when the south western monsoon finally arrived here in Delhi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Art</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/pixel-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/pixel-art/</guid>
      <description>This post was originally made on my blogger blog on 01/04/2022. In this post, I shall be expressing my newfound appreciation of Pixel art.&#xA;Personally, I have always been a fan of old 90&amp;rsquo;s graphics and retro computing in general. Old 90&amp;rsquo;s graphics, although a compromise made by the artists for the days low graphics memory have in this age become something people appreciate. Afterall, it still is an art. And what an art !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearing A Mechanical Watch</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/mechanical-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 17:30:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/mechanical-watch/</guid>
      <description>This article was made on my old blog on 17 February 2022.&#xA;Having worn almost all sorts of watches, around a month ago I finally decided to make the leap to a mechanical watch. This leap of mine which truly felt like a leap of faith in the beginning, was a lot more reliable than I had expected it to be.&#xA;The one thing that attracted me towards a mechanical watch is the fact that it has life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parantha Teir List</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/parantha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 17:31:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/parantha/</guid>
      <description>This post was originally published on my blogger blog on 6 February 2022. This is a revised version of that post.&#xA;The perfect north Indian breakfast, not just north Indian though. Parantha is a thing that possibly is the largest common tie between one of the largest regions of this sub continent. From Lahore to Calcutta, you can see the similar breakfast of parantas with chai. And why not !? isn&amp;rsquo;t it such a great one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Only Day Your Dad Will Ever Ask You To Watch TV</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/republic-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:30:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/republic-day/</guid>
      <description>This post was originally published on 27 January 2022 on my old blog. This is a revised version of the post.&#xA;Republic Day, its like the only time of the year when your dad asks you to watch TV. Or shall I say that wants you to watch TV with him. For all my life republic day has always been a father son moment type of a thing. Spotting celebrity faces in the republic day crowd, to guessing the aircraft names during fly-by&amp;rsquo;s, and having the annual moment where the Arjun tank comes on screen during the parade (and my dad has to specifically inform me about it&amp;rsquo;s arrival) has always kind of been how I&amp;rsquo;ve had and seen Republic Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharatchandra</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/sharatchandra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/sharatchandra/</guid>
      <description>I own the red one, my friend owns the blue one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Gate, Gaussian Noise Edit</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/tree/</guid>
      <description>A gaussian noise edit of India Gate. Inspired by the Molchat Doma album art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCDC Building, Gaussian Noise Edit</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/image/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/image/</guid>
      <description>A gaussian noise edit of the brutalist NCDC head office complex located in Central Delhi. Just take a bus to Palika Kendra, and you shall see for yourself. This brutalist building that once dominated the area is now overshadowed by the ones near it. Yet it stands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/gallery/physics/</guid>
      <description>Found at Central Library, Shahbad Engineering College</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
