<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on arjun&#39;s webpage</title>
    <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on arjun&#39;s webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:33:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cipirit.netlify.app/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music Reaction Channels</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/music-reaction-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:33:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/music-reaction-channels/</guid>
      <description>In the recent years, music reaction channels on YouTube have become quite a thing. These channels mainly react to forms of alternative music such as rock, metal and other genres that like to go with the &amp;ldquo;its not pop music&amp;rdquo; identity.
Cultural Shock The usual consumer base of this media, largely comprises of nerdy, introverted, and in recent years (due to the desensitization of the word nerd) autistic people, which in turn largely contains Caucasian males.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Day Your Dad Will Ever Ask You To Watch TV</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/republic-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:30:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/republic-day/</guid>
      <description>This post was originally published on 27 January 2022 on my old blog. This is a revised version of the post.
Republic Day, its like the only time of the year when your dad asks you to watch TV. Or shall I say that wants you to watch TV with him. For all my life republic day has always been a father son moment type of a thing. Spotting celebrity faces in the republic day crowd, to guessing the aircraft names during fly-by&amp;rsquo;s, and having the annual moment where the Arjun tank comes on screen during the parade (and my dad has to specifically inform me about it&amp;rsquo;s arrival) has always kind of been how I&amp;rsquo;ve had and seen Republic Day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
