<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>College on arjun&#39;s webpage</title>
    <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/tags/college/</link>
    <description>Recent content in College on arjun&#39;s webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:32:11 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cipirit.netlify.app/tags/college/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Disconnect</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/disconnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/disconnect/</guid>
      <description>Music, Mathematics and The Matrix&#xA;Earphones are like parasites. Parasites that crawl up your ear to disconnect you from the reality to hook you up to the fake world of digital entertainment stimulating your senses shielding you from the truth you are trying to run away from. Remember that old Moserbear advertisement ?&#xA;Don&#39;t like to think too much It makes me think too much It keeps my mind on my mind Don&#39;t want to see too much It makes me see too much Sometimes I&#39;d rather be blind Music itself is a very powerful thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:31:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/college/</guid>
      <description>A series of (incoherent) thoughts I have had since joining college. The curiculum is merely a carcass every student is assigned to drag behind them for the next four years of their life. Even the administration knows this, and they dont put too much effort into not letting the world know about it.&#xA;Exams and academics only exist to provide a goal to those who dont have a purpose to live upto (yet).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Jee Feels</title>
      <link>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/post-jee-feels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 17:31:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipirit.netlify.app/posts/post-jee-feels/</guid>
      <description>So my first JEE attempt is complete and now I am here, writing a blog post in a (sucessfull) attempt of relaxing and chilling for one day in what seems like months since I have walked without a head full of stress. This I belive must be my reward. The only proof that I need to strengthen this belife is that today, ladies and gentlemen is the day when the south western monsoon finally arrived here in Delhi.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
